Guide to the Department of Athletics, Yale University, Records of the Women's Crew Team
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Department of Athletics, Yale University, records of the women's crew team
1973-2000
RU 242
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
2.75
The records consist of the Yale women's crew team captains' log books, and administrative records.
Yale University. Dept. of Athletics, Physical Education, and Recreation
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 38-B (YRG 38-B), Records documenting specific sports at Yale.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the records is restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by topic.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of the Yale women's crew team captains' log books, and administrative records.
College sports; Rowing; Yale University -- Rowing; Yale University -- Sports; Yale University. Dept. of Athletics, Physical Education, and Recreation
- Women's crew captain's logbooks, 1973-2000; Accession 2000-A-069
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2035
  - Captain's logbooks, 1973-2000 (Box 1)
  - Captain's logbooks, 1973-2000 (Box 2)
- Records of the women's crew team, 1977-1997; Accession 2006-A-014
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2032
  Scope and Contents
  Arranged by topic.
  - Association, 1981-1989 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, 1987-1990 (Box 1)
  - General, 1981-1987 (Box 1)
  - Post Season, 1987 (Box 1)
  - Publications, 1977-1997 (Box 1)
  - Reports, 1982, 1988, 1990
  - Sculling Development Camp, 1990 (Box 1)
  - Search -Assistant Crew Coach, 1980-1981 (Box 1)